{
    "id": "4c50f06f7b874f8fa74454dc72e586c3",
    "title": "Supply suitable conjunctions",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "dfa79913b8fe4c0faa68aa389b655ef9",
            "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Walk carefully ………………. you should fall.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "lest",
                        "otherwise",
                        "if"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………….. he saw me, he started yelling.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "No sooner than",
                        "As soon as",
                        "Hardly"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "……………… did the police reach the spot than the crowd dispersed.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "No sooner",
                        "As soon as",
                        "Hardly"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is the same crook ………….. cheated me last year.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "that",
                        "which",
                        "whom"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is honest ………………… industrious.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "also",
                        "as well as",
                        "as well"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………. harshly your parents may treat you, you must respect them.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "However",
                        "Though",
                        "As though"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Wise men seek knowledge …………….. the ignorant shun it.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "when",
                        "however",
                        "whereas"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "She asked me ……………….. I could lend her my camera.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "if",
                        "in case",
                        "unless"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He had hardly recovered from pneumonia, …………….. he suffered a heart attack.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "when",
                        "than",
                        "while"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "A Rajput soldier ……………….. die than surrender.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "would",
                        "would rather",
                        "rather"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}